kegerator.com 2014-11-21

# CS: Other Information: Privacy Policy

## Your Personal Information

We at CompactAppliance.Com recognize your right to privacy and are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect on our site to provide you with a superior shopping experience. When you order, we will ask for information that will ensure that your order is processed in an accurate, secure, and timely manner. Information we ask for includes your name, e-mail address, contact phone number, mailing and billing address, and credit card number and expiration date. In fulfilling your order, we only share your personal information with outside parties to the extent necessary to fulfill your order. We may also run contests on our web site in which we ask visitors for contact information that includes name, address, and e-mail address. This information is used to contact contestants if they should win. We will use your email to periodically send you our e-mail newsletter that contains special offers and updates about our products and services. You may opt-out of receiving these emails and you may modify your contact information at any time. 

You will receive administrative emails regarding your order that cannot be opt-ed out of. The first email you receive will serve as receipt of your order. The information included in this email consists of sales price, order number, and shipping information. You will receive a second email when your order ships. This will contain all tracking information so that you will be able to locate the status of your order at any time. 

We protect your account information against unauthorized access or release. We do reserve the right to share your information with third party partners that we have approved. Outside of this scenario, we will not give, sell, rent, or loan any identifiable personal information to a third party unless you have authorized us or we are legally required to do so. 

## Cookies

To personalize your experience at CompactAppliance.Com, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a cookie. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and power other services like writing a review. By disabling cookies you will not be able to use the shopping cart feature on the [CompactAppliance.com](http://www.compactappliance.com/) web site. 

## Log Files

Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart. We use IP addresses, referring/exit pages, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any personal, identifiable information. 

## Live Chat Help

CompactAppliance.com incorporates a live chat option on its website. A third party service provider powers the chat functionality. Information obtained through this order form of communication may not be used or shared with the third party hosting the software. 

## Links to/from Other Sites

To enhance your shopping experience, the CompactAppliance.Com site may have links to other sites on the internet that are owned by third party vendors and other third parties (External Sites), or you may come to CompactAppliance.com from a link from an external site. The other web sites will have their own rules on privacy that you should review. [CompactAppliance.com](http://www.compactappliance.com/) is not responsible for the privacy policies of external sites. 

## Correcting, Updating, Deactivating

There are several ways to update information you have provided CompactAppliance.Com: 

  * Email [info@CompactAppliance.com](mailto:info@CompactAppliance.com) to update or change any information you may have provided us. 
  * Email [optout@CompactAppliance.com](mailto:optout@CompactAppliance.com) to be removed from our newsletter 
  * Call toll free at [1-800-297-6076](tel:1-800-297-6076)
  * You may also respond to the email with "Remove" or "Unsubscribe" in the subject line to be removed from any future newsletters. 

## Sweepstakes

CompactAppliance.com offers sweepstakes on its web site. Any information collected in registering for these sweepstakes is used to contact individuals should they win. We will also use your email address to send you a newsletter containing information on specials and events. You may opt-out of receiving notices by indicating "Remove" or "Unsubscribe" in the subject line. 

## Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. Our shopping cart incorporates industry-standard secure server software (Secure Socket Layers / SSL) provided by [Verisign](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&dn=www.CompactAppliance.com&lang=en) into sensitive sections of our store. All online transactions at CompactAppliance.Com are handled using this encryption technology. When you enter your credit card number into the order form, it is transmitted across the internet in an encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets out. For added security, we also encrypt the credit card number when it is stored on disk. 

To verify that we use Verisign SSL technology, you may click on the Verisign logo below: 

Paymentech Services, a state-of-the-art credit card verification service, keeps CompactAppliance.Com's transactions secure by encrypting all of your personal information while validating the transaction. We use RSA encryption technology to scramble your data so that it would be virtually impossible to break into. 

There are two ways to make sure you are browsing secure pages. Both Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator indicate secure modes with a symbol - the image of a closed padlock. You will know the information is protected if the closed-lock symbol pops into view in the lower right or left-hand corner of your screen while you are checking it out. You can also verify secure pages by checking the address, or URL, listed on the scroll bar. If you spot an "s"after the "http" at the beginning of the address, you know that you're browsing in a secure environment. 

## Federal Law Limits Your Liability

Federal law limits an individual's liability if their credit card information should ever fall into the wrong hands. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act of 1975, you may dispute the charges on your account with your credit card company and temporarily withhold payment while they investigate the situation. Even if your creditor disagrees that unauthorized purchases were made, you're generally only liable for the first $50 in fraudulent charges. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under any circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. However, if you have opted out of communication with the site then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used in this new manner. Users will have a choice whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
